(Penny:)Just a sec.
Theater's above a bowling alley
so it's a little noisy...
(Penny:)...but it might be the only chance
I'll ever get to play Anne Frank.
(Penny:)And the director is brilliant.
(Penny:)He uses the bowling sounds
as, like, Nazi artillery.
(Penny:)Okay, great, I'll see you then.
(Leonard:)- Hello?
SHELDON: Okay, step four.
(Sheldon:)Do you see that small plastic case
on my dresser?
(Penny:)Your dresser? Who is this?
(Sheldon:)It's Sheldon.
PENNY: Oh, hey, Sheldon.
How's San Francisco?
(Sheldon:)I'm not in San Francisco. I'm on a tra...
Were you even listening to me?
- No, I was talking to my friend. What's up?
- What's up? I'll tell you what's up.
(Sheldon:)I'm in a crisis situation...
(Sheldon:)...I need you to marshal your powers
of concentration, limited as they may be...
(Leonard:)Give me the phone.
(Leonard:)Hi, Penny, it's Leonard.
(Penny:)Hey, Leonard, what's going on
with Dr. Wackadoodle?
He's calling to ask you a favor.
You might be confused...
...because he didn't use the words "Penny,"
"Sheldon," "please" or "favor."